<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datasheet>
  <Product>
    <Name>Composition Engine</Name>
    <Version>0.5.0</Version>
    <Tagline>Turn Data into Documents.</Tagline>
    <Subtitle>Fast. Scalable. Just HTML & CSS.</Subtitle>
  </Product>
  <Intro>
    The Composition Engine bridges the gap between raw data (XML) and professional documents (PDF). It is designed to process massive datasets efficiently, producing pixel-perfect documents using HTML templates and headless browser rendering. Stop fighting with archaic formats like XSL-FO or proprietary tools. Build your invoices, statements, and reports using the web technologies you already know.
  </Intro>
  <Features>
    <Feature>
      <Title>High Fidelity Rendering</Title>
      <Description>Uses a headless browser (Puppeteer) to render full HTML/CSS, ensuring your PDFs look exactly like your web templates. What you see is what you get.</Description>
    </Feature>
    <Feature>
      <Title>Handlebars Templates</Title>
      <Description>Full support for logic ({{#if}}, {{#each}}) and formatting helpers (formatCurrency, formatDate) to handle complex data requirements.</Description>
    </Feature>
    <Feature>
      <Title>Scalable Streaming</Title>
      <Description>Processes gigabyte-sized XML files with millions of records without loading the entire file into memory. Flat memory usage regardless of input size.</Description>
    </Feature>
    <Feature>
      <Title>Flexible Output Modes</Title>
      <Description>Generate individual PDF files for each record (Multi Mode) or combine all records into a single giant PDF (Single Mode).</Description>
    </Feature>
    <Feature>
      <Title>High Concurrency</Title>
      <Description>Parallel processing maximizes CPU usage and throughput by utilizing a robust pool of browser instances.</Description>
    </Feature>
    <Feature>
      <Title>Dynamic Charts</Title>
      <Description>Embed data-driven charts directly in your documents.</Description>
    </Feature>
  </Features>
  <Requirements>
    <Requirement>Deno Runtime (v2.5 or later)</Requirement>
    <Requirement>Google Chrome, Chromium, or Microsoft Edge</Requirement>
    <Requirement>Windows, macOS, or Linux</Requirement>
    <Requirement>Multi-core Processor (2+ cores, 4+ recommended)</Requirement>
    <Requirement>Minimum 4GB RAM (8GB recommended for high concurrency)</Requirement>
  </Requirements>
  <Pricing>
    <Tier>
      <Name>Developer</Name>
      <Price>Free</Price>
      <Description>Open Source (MIT License). Perfect for local development and small projects.</Description>
    </Tier>
    <Tier>
      <Name>Enterprise</Name>
      <Price>Contact Us</Price>
      <Description>Dedicated support, SLA, and custom integration services.</Description>
    </Tier>
  </Pricing>
  <Contact>
    <Website>https://composition-engine.com</Website>
    <Email>support@composition-engine.com</Email>
  </Contact>
</Datasheet>
